var questions = [
    {
        "question": "苹果",
        "options": [
            "banana",
            "apple",
            "pear",
            "keyboard"
        ],
        "answer": "apple"
    },
    {
        "question": "橙子",
        "options": [
            "orange",
            "oaange",
            "orang",
            "orage"
        ],
        "answer": "orange"
    },
    {
        "question": "mouse",
        "options": ["鼠标", "番薯", "红薯", "属地"],
        "answer": "鼠标"
    },
    {
        "question": "电脑",
        "options": ["computer", "bag", "desk", "map"],
        "answer": "computer"
    },
    {
        "question": "书",
        "options": ["book", "bok", "block", "note"],
        "answer": "book"
    },
    {
        "question": "eraser",
        "options": ["橡皮擦", "橡皮刀", "橡皮圈", "橡皮胶"],
        "answer": "橡皮擦"
    },
    {
        "question": "pen",
        "options": ["钢笔", "铅笔", "圆珠笔", "毛笔"],
        "answer": "钢笔"
    },
    {
        "question": "钟",
        "options": ["clock", "cloud", "code", "change"],
        "answer": "clock"
    },
    {
        "question": "数字",
        "options": ["number", "name", "nike", "nice"],
        "answer": "number"
    },
    {
        "question": "班级",
        "options": ["class", "glass", "hass", "css"],
        "answer": "班级"
    }
];